{"sections":{"main":{"type":"rich-text","blocks":{"heading":{"type":"heading","settings":{"heading":"","heading_size":"h3"}}},"block_order":["heading"],"settings":{"alignment":"center","width":"small","margin_top":"xs","margin_bottom":"xs"}},"collapsible-content":{"type":"collapsible-content","blocks":{"accordion-1":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"WHEN WILL I RECEIVE MY ORDER?","answer":"<p>Orders are processed Monday - Friday, excluding major holidays, and shipped within 1-3 business days.<\/p>"}},"accordion-2":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"WHAT IS YOUR RETURN POLICY?","answer":"<p>You have up to 14 days upon receiving shipment to return items purchased on www.alphastyle.store. Shipping Charges are non-refundable. Item(s) must be in new, unused condition with original tags still attached. Undergarments, swimwear, and fragrance cannot be returned due to our hygiene policy.<br\/><br\/>We do not accept returns or exchanges for AlphaStyle products not purchased from www.alphastyle.store. All other purchases from third-party retailers or Chapter Stores, please contact the retailer directly for their return policy.<\/p>"}},"accordion_CefDCX":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"HOW DO I RETURN MY ORDER?","answer":"<p>Please email us at cs@alphastylestore.com with details.<\/p>"}},"accordion_iHDeC6":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"CAN I CANCEL MY ORDER?","answer":"<p>Requesting a cancellation is not guaranteed. During Peak periods and orders placed over the weekend, cancellations may not be possible. Please email us at cs@alphastylestore.com for details.<\/p>"}},"accordion_XYaWJV":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"HOW DO I KNOW THE ITEM WILL FIT ME?","answer":"<p>Every product page has a size chart and details of the size worn by the model in the product description. Our Customer Support team is available to answer any questions regarding measurements and fitting.<\/p>"}},"accordion_RKpMLA":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"HOW DO I FIND OUT WHEN NEW STYLES ARE RELEASED?","answer":"<p>Subscribe to our Newsletter or follow us on Instagram for early release information.<\/p>"}},"accordion_XL6QNB":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"WHAT IF I NEED TO MODIFY\/ADJUST MY ORDER?","answer":"<p>Once an order has been placed, it cannot be modified or adjusted. By completing your purchase you agree to our terms and conditions and cancellations are not guaranteed.<\/p>"}},"accordion_6xBqV4":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"MY ORDER HAS BEEN CANCELED, HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE FOR THE REFUND TO PROCESS?","answer":"<p>Allow 48-72 hours for processing. Refunds are issued during business days.<\/p>"}},"accordion_wfqzEQ":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"MY TRACKING INFORMATION STATES THAT MY ORDER WAS DELIVERED. WHAT DO I DO IF I HAVEN'T RECEIVED IT?","answer":"<p>Allow 48 hours after the stated delivery time. If your package has still not been delivered, contact us for assistance at cs@alphastylestore.com.<\/p>"}},"accordion_JM8W6C":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"I EMAILED CUSTOMER SUPPORT, WHEN CAN I EXPECT A RESPONSE?","answer":"<p>Expect a response within 24-72 business hours from our Customer Support Team. Response times may be delayed during peak periods.<\/p>"}},"accordion_9WBAt9":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"HOW DO I UPDATE AN INCORRECT SHIPPING ADDRESS?","answer":"<p>Address updates can be requested but are not guaranteed. We strongly suggest double checking information before submitting your order. By completing your purchase you agree to our terms and conditions and address updates are not guaranteed.<\/p>"}},"accordion_HtWqmj":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"I PLACED MULTIPLE ORDERS, CAN I COMBINE THEM?","answer":"<p>Once your order is placed we are unable to combine shipments on multiple orders.<\/p>"}},"accordion_j9prLM":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"I DIDN'T RECEIVE A TRACKING NUMBER, WHEN SHOULD I EXPECT IT?","answer":"<p>A shipping confirmation email is sent once your order has shipped. Allow 3-5 business days to process your order.<\/p>"}},"accordion_kFyfrU":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"I RECEIVED A TRACKING NUMBER, BUT THE SHIPMENT HASN’T MOVED.","answer":"<p>Tracking numbers are generated when your shipping label is created. Please allow 1-3 business days from the courier for tracking updates.<\/p>"}},"accordion_NWKJrf":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"WHAT SHOULD I DO IF I RECEIVED A DAMAGED PRODUCT?","answer":"<p>Email us at cs@alphastylestore.com within 24-48 hours of delivery with detailed images of the product(s) in question and the packing\/invoice slip. Our team will investigate the situation and respond with a resolution.<\/p>"}},"accordion_y4bGQy":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"CAN I RETURN ITEMS PURCHASED DURING SALE PERIODS?","answer":"<p>All sale items must be returned within 14 days of receiving. If there is a genuine fault with the item AlphaStyle must be notified within the 14 days.<\/p>"}},"accordion_WQtHYP":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"I RECEIVED AN ITEM FROM ALPHASTYLE.STORE AS A GIFT. CAN I RETURN IT OR EXCHANGE IT?","answer":"<p>You will have to contact the purchaser to return the product and purchase the updated item we have in stock. We do not offer exchanges.<\/p>"}},"accordion_rBBHiC":{"type":"accordion","settings":{"question":"DO YOU OFFER GIFT RECEIPTS?","answer":"<p>We do not offer gift receipts.<\/p>"}}},"block_order":["accordion-1","accordion-2","accordion_CefDCX","accordion_iHDeC6","accordion_XYaWJV","accordion_RKpMLA","accordion_XL6QNB","accordion_6xBqV4","accordion_wfqzEQ","accordion_JM8W6C","accordion_9WBAt9","accordion_HtWqmj","accordion_j9prLM","accordion_kFyfrU","accordion_NWKJrf","accordion_y4bGQy","accordion_WQtHYP","accordion_rBBHiC"],"settings":{"aspect_ratio":"medium","heading":"FAQs","heading_size":"h2","enable_animation":true,"slideshow_speed":4,"button_label":"","button_link":"","button_style":"simple","margin_top":"no-indent","margin_bottom":"m"}}},"order":["main","collapsible-content"]}